<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>boxmein</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on boxmein</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boxmein.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KalmarCTF 2023 - EZ Web - Writeup</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-ezweb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-ezweb/</guid><description>I participated in KalmarCTF as part of team Kassipojad :cat2:. One of the best CTFs I&amp;rsquo;ve ever played!!
Here&amp;rsquo;s a writeup of the EZ Web task, or rather a dump of the notes I took:
What do we know? URL https://www.caddy.chal-kalmarc.tf/flag.txt returns 403 https://php.caddy.chal-kalmarc.tf/flag.txt https://php.caddy.chal-kalmarc.tf/index.php https://static.caddy.chal-kalmarc.tf/logo_round.svg Source is included compose file includes some backup step Backups folder includes the host cp -r *.caddy.chal-kalmarc.tf backups/ &amp;amp;&amp;amp; rm php.caddy.chal-kalmarc.tf/flag.txt &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sleep 1 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; caddy run Can use slashes in host Caddy v1 has an admin API on a separate port Caddy matchers (respond /flag.</description></item><item><title>KalmarCTF 2023 - Invoiced - Writeup</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-invoiced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-invoiced/</guid><description>Final working payload Name: a&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;&amp;lt;meta http-equiv=&amp;quot;Refresh&amp;quot; content=&amp;quot;0; url='http://127.0.0.1:5000/orders'&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;
Others: empty
What we know Download source Read files: payments.js - get discount code FREEZTUFSSZ1412 app.js - get the implementation GET /cart =&amp;gt; show form to post to checkout POST /checkout =&amp;gt; visit url, turn to pdf pdf impl: open puppeteer, visit /renderInvoice?name=&amp;hellip;, wait for networkidle0, bake to pdf GET /renderInvoice =&amp;gt; replace variables in template URL parameters are rendered without escaping =&amp;gt; XSS GET /orders =&amp;gt; return flag Find unique safety features: /renderInvoice has: CSP default-src unsafe-inline maxcdn.</description></item><item><title>KalmarCTF 2023 - kalmarunionen-fun - Writeup</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-kalmarunionen-fun/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-kalmarunionen-fun/</guid><description>Learnings Don&amp;rsquo;t overthink it - we were about to cross reference Harry Potter spells Keep your old code around - my renderer was based on a 2014 project which really sped up the prototyping Live for this moment: Writeup We found a bunch of data of a rumored accelerometer My first instinct was to render it Maybe my first instinct should&amp;rsquo;ve been to make a kalman filter to smooth out the true position&amp;hellip; I rendered it It was really painful to watch 2.</description></item><item><title>KalmarCTF 2023 - renaissance-flag-music - writeup</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-renaissance-flag-music/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2023-03-05-kalmarctf-renaissance-flag-music/</guid><description>What we did It was mostly google-fu or having sufficient previous background knowledge (e.g. someone who has studied music or has played guitar)
Detect that WeirdTable.png maps chords to letters
Detect that FlagMusic.png is some musical notation &amp;hellip; renaissance music? &amp;hellip; look up renaissance notation =&amp;gt; find French lute tablature so it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a French lute tab empty=X, A=open, B=1st fret, C=2nd, &amp;hellip; ok so&amp;hellip; what is the tuning?
French lutes are tuned how?</description></item><item><title>Tartu CTF 2018 - Writeup</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2018-11-03-tartu-ctf-2018-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2018-11-03-tartu-ctf-2018-writeup/</guid><description>I participated in a cybersecurity contest called a CTF (for capture the flag). It&amp;rsquo;s a format of a security game where contestants have to attack a web or other type of server, and to prove their progress in breaking the server, they submit text strings called &amp;ldquo;flags&amp;rdquo; found at various steps of progress.
In the Tartu CTF 2018, we were playing the Game of Thrones CTF. At the start of the contest, we were given an IP address and nothing else.</description></item><item><title>Hack The Box: Poison - Writeup</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2018-09-02-hack-the-box-poison-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2018-09-02-hack-the-box-poison-writeup/</guid><description>NOTE: we did that in CyberCamp 2018. Just re-solving it. IP: 10.10.10.84
nmap Scanning 10.10.10.84 [65536 ports] Discovered open port 80/tcp on 10.10.10.84 Discovered open port 22/tcp on 10.10.10.84
Web server Web server has a bunch of &amp;ldquo;testing PHP scripts&amp;rdquo;.
One of the scripts is called listfiles.php, which lists the folder.
Among the PHP files there&amp;rsquo;s also a file called pwdbackup.txt:
This password is secure, it&amp;#39;s encoded atleast 13 times.. what could go wrong really.</description></item><item><title>Path Planning &amp;amp; Trajectory Generation in C++</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-09-30-path-planning-trajectory-generation-in-c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-09-30-path-planning-trajectory-generation-in-c/</guid><description>This is a writeup of the Self-Driving Car Engineer Nanodegree Term 3 Path Planning project. It was very challenging to say the least, but with the approach presented in the walkthrough, I quickly made headway. It also outlined important implementation details such as working relative to the end of the path instead of the car, and reusing path points from previous iterations of the simulator.
Check out my source code.</description></item><item><title>Unscented Kalman Filters</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-08-19-unscented-kalman-filters/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-08-19-unscented-kalman-filters/</guid><description>This post is about the Unscented Kalman Filters project. Unscented Kalman Filters are like a Level 2 version of Extended Kalman Filters.
When my code (hopefully) passes review, I&amp;rsquo;ve finished Term 2 of the Nanodegree. (I&amp;rsquo;ve been pushing forward for 7 months even though it feels like I just applied to enter the Nanodegree!)
Here&amp;rsquo;s a video of the Unscented Kalman Filter doing what it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to.
The red and blue dots are noisy sensor data, while the green dots are the Kalman filter deciding the car is somewhere in the middle of the sensor data.</description></item><item><title>Using PID to drive like Vin Diesel</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-08-06-using-pid-to-drive-like-vin-diesel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-08-06-using-pid-to-drive-like-vin-diesel/</guid><description>I just finished the PID controller project of the Udacity Self-Driving Car Nanodegree!
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SrdFTXpXkR4
The challenge was simple - make this car go around the track, when the simulator will tell you how far off you are.
To do this, especially since the simulator tells us an error metric, I needed to build a PID controller.
A PID controller is a simple function that relates the error (how off we are from our trajectory) to a control variable (throttle/steering/&amp;hellip;).</description></item><item><title>Using Particle Filters to localize a car in 2D space</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-07-29-using-particle-filters-to-localize-a-car-in-2d-space/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-07-29-using-particle-filters-to-localize-a-car-in-2d-space/</guid><description>This is a discussion on how I implemented and finished the Particle Filters project in the Udacity Self-Driving Car Engineer Nanodegree.
The challenge Given a map of the world (a bunch of landmarks), and the car drawing lines to all landmarks within range with noisy data, give the best assumption for the car&amp;rsquo;s position in the world.
The process How I was going to solve it was with an approach called particle filters.</description></item><item><title>Using Extended Kalman Filters for object tracking</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-06-04-using-extended-kalman-filters-for-object-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-06-04-using-extended-kalman-filters-for-object-tracking/</guid><description>This is a discussion of how I solved the Extended Kalman Filters project in the Udacity Self-Driving Car Engineer Nanodegree.
The problem Our car has two sensors: a lidar and a radar. Both can see a pedestrian. Based on the lidar and radar data (both a bit noisy), keep track of the pedestrian&amp;rsquo;s position and velocity.
The solution Kalman filters offer a solution that can combine both lidar and radar data to complement each other, and a robust object-tracking model that also keeps track of the error margins.</description></item><item><title>Writeup: Vehicle Detection</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-04-28-writeup-vehicle-detection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-04-28-writeup-vehicle-detection/</guid><description>Vehicle Detection Project** This is a writeup for my Vehicle Detection project.
Goals The goals / steps of this project are the following:
Perform a Histogram of Oriented Gradients (HOG) feature extraction on a labeled training set of images and train a classifier Linear SVM classifier Optionally, you can also apply a color transform and append binned color features, as well as histograms of color, to your HOG feature vector. Note: for those first two steps don&amp;rsquo;t forget to normalize your features and randomize a selection for training and testing.</description></item><item><title>Writeup: Advanced Lane Finding</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-04-21-writeup-advanced-lane-finding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-04-21-writeup-advanced-lane-finding/</guid><description>Advanced Lane Finding Project The goals / steps of this project are the following:
Compute the camera calibration matrix and distortion coefficients given a set of chessboard images. Apply a distortion correction to raw images. Use color transforms, gradients, etc., to create a thresholded binary image. Apply a perspective transform to rectify binary image (&amp;ldquo;birds-eye view&amp;rdquo;). Detect lane pixels and fit to find the lane boundary. Determine the curvature of the lane and vehicle position with respect to center.</description></item><item><title>Writeup: Behavioral Cloning</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-03-31-writeup-behavioral-cloning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-03-31-writeup-behavioral-cloning/</guid><description>This one-to-one copy of my writeup for Udacity follows the format in the writeup template, hopefully making the writeup more thorough and easier to grade. It follows a pretty strict format, but includes a lot of interesting content. Behavioral Cloning Project
The goals / steps of this project are the following:
Use the simulator to collect data of good driving behavior Build, a convolution neural network in Keras that predicts steering angles from images Train and validate the model with a training and validation set Test that the model successfully drives around track one without leaving the road Summarize the results with a written report Rubric Points Here I will consider the rubric points individually and describe how I addressed each point in my implementation.</description></item><item><title>Writeup: Traffic Sign Classifier</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-03-09-writeup-traffic-sign-classifier/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-03-09-writeup-traffic-sign-classifier/</guid><description>This is a one-to-one copy of the writeup for my traffic sign classifier.
Rubric This is a per-point addressment of the Udacity review rubric. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of like filling a form instead of writing freeform text, but I hope reviewing the document is therefore easier and more structured.
A reference to the rubric is visible here: rubric.
Writeup 1. Provide a Writeup that includes all the rubric points and how you addressed each one.</description></item><item><title>SDCND: Lane Line Detection</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-01-25-sdcnd-lane-line-detection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-01-25-sdcnd-lane-line-detection/</guid><description>The self-driving Car Engineer Nanodegree (I&amp;rsquo;ll just use SDCND from here) is a huge Udacity course about self-driving cars starting from vision ending with robotics. I applied in October, having an incredible opportunity to participate since Jan 19.
The first project of the SDCND is about lane line detection. This is a simple experiment in computer vision using straight line detection and averaging to detect the left and right lane separators.</description></item><item><title>Why your Estonian ID card won't register in OSX Keychain Access</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-01-03-why-your-estonian-id-card-wont-register-in-osx-keychain-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2017-01-03-why-your-estonian-id-card-wont-register-in-osx-keychain-access/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer and once tried to login via SSH to your virtual server, this might be why you can&amp;rsquo;t sign in to online services anymore.
The symptoms aren&amp;rsquo;t really obvious - you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to sign in to banks or other services. Swedbank prompts you with a &amp;ldquo;Kasutaja tuvastamine ebaõnnestus&amp;rdquo; while eesti.ee will show a SSL_CLIENT_AUTH_CERT_NEEDED error. When you open Keychain Access, the card will not be listed on top on the left sidebar (above the login keychain).</description></item><item><title>How to Drive a Relay with Raspberry Pi</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2016-08-20-how-to-drive-a-relay-with-raspberry-pi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2016-08-20-how-to-drive-a-relay-with-raspberry-pi/</guid><description>So, you got yourself a Raspberry Pi and were wondering what the hell one could do with all those different pins. You read something about a &amp;ldquo;relay&amp;rdquo; - a switch that you can operate with low power to control a circuit with bigger power, and bought one or even two. You sort of looked at the specs of the thing, mostly the &amp;ldquo;wow, this can relay a 230V voltage!&amp;rdquo; aspect, and bought two to attach to your Pi.</description></item><item><title>Playstation Portable: Day 1</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2016-01-23-playstation-portable-day-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2016-01-23-playstation-portable-day-1/</guid><description>This is a new project I&amp;rsquo;m literally working on at this very moment. So I got a Playstation Portable as a gift from a friend, who didn&amp;rsquo;t need it herself. My plan is to crack it, load a bunch of cool programs on it and also try to make it fly a camera drone (someday&amp;hellip;)
It&amp;rsquo;s a model 1004, which stands for the &amp;ldquo;phat&amp;rdquo; version. Shortly, this is the oldest model of the PSP, released in 2004.</description></item><item><title>repost: "I have nothing to hide so I don't care about computer security"</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-22-repost-i-have-nothing-to-hide-so-i-dont-care-about-computer-security/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-22-repost-i-have-nothing-to-hide-so-i-dont-care-about-computer-security/</guid><description>I live in a country generally assumed to be a dictatorship. One of the Arab spring countries. I have lived through curfews and have seen the outcomes of the sort of surveillance now being revealed in the US. People here talking about curfews aren&amp;rsquo;t realizing what that actually FEELS like. It isn&amp;rsquo;t about having to go inside, and the practicality of that. It&amp;rsquo;s about creating the feeling that everyone, everything is watching.</description></item><item><title>I've Totally Also Written Stuff Here</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-20-ive-totally-also-written-stuff-here/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-20-ive-totally-also-written-stuff-here/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve also written a few guides strictly related to The Powder Toy - those will bore everyone else other than TPT players.
How To Make Custom Brush Shapes for Powder Toy How To Install The Powder Toy (And The Unofficial Script Manager)</description></item><item><title>colorsplash</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-16-colorsplash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-16-colorsplash/</guid><description>look at this thing I made: http://boxmein.net/tests/colorsplash
it&amp;rsquo;s a weird test of CSS3 animations, material design colors and god-awful centering tricks. whoever invented CSS clearly did not want people to center things :D</description></item><item><title>Some Older Posts May Be Found Here</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-16-some-older-posts-may-be-found-here/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2015-08-16-some-older-posts-may-be-found-here/</guid><description>https://ello.co/boxmein/post/b7ZbXSWA6mdvOm-yVlOX4Q https://ello.co/boxmein/post/q1JPmFszvVtCS4Tw7S-Ekw https://ello.co/boxmein/post/WwZqe35COia-946vSr5tlA https://ello.co/boxmein/post/_uS1i4qA2cVXbbPmAfpzww https://ello.co/boxmein/post/mm40pK6TbUO9s7-mkk_goA Things Can Also Be Found On My Actual Website:
http://boxmein.net</description></item><item><title>#powder brainfuck preprocessor</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2013-09-27-powder-brainfuck-preprocessor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2013-09-27-powder-brainfuck-preprocessor/</guid><description>Another pointless ordeal into esoteric languages: it converts #powder nicknames into Brainfuck characters, which can be run from a brainfuck interpreter.
[gist https://gist.github.com/boxmein/6729923 /]
Its main inspiration was #powder as well:
[16:52.19] boxmein: proramming lang made from IRC nicks from this chan [16:52.26] boxmein: do eet [16:52.29] no? [16:52.34] boxmein: do it [16:52.36] smart quotes are like /* and */ [16:52.36] &amp;gt;pastes code [16:52.39] &amp;gt;mass highlight
so lol</description></item><item><title>Unnecessary Programming Language</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2013-09-17-unnecessary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2013-09-17-unnecessary/</guid><description>I made the most pointless esoteric language interpreter today. It&amp;rsquo;s for the language called Unnecessary, which basically is this:
Unnecessary is a programming language from 2005 by Keymaker where the existence of a program file is considered an error. The valid Unnecessary program file extension is &amp;lsquo;unn&amp;rsquo;. However, if there is no program file, the interpreter or compiler can work normally and perform a nop.
So basically if the file exists you&amp;rsquo;re having an error.</description></item><item><title>Words that don't share letters with US state names</title><link>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2013-09-17-words-that-dont-share-letters-with-us-state-names/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boxmein.github.io/posts/2013-09-17-words-that-dont-share-letters-with-us-state-names/</guid><description>A while ago an interesting question was posed in a comment thread, to which I, being someone not from the US who couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember state names, wanted an answer to in the easiest way possible.
So what do I do? I write a script for it. In Ruby.
The script follows:
[gist https://gist.github.com/boxmein/6136291 /]
Really basic. I go through each of the arguments passed in the command line, each of the state names and just try if something doesn&amp;rsquo;t share letters with a state it outputs both strings.</description></item></channel></rss>